<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2014-10-06T10:54:55.452-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="menzor"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2014-10-06T10:56:27.979-04:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="menzor"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:scaffolding="/etc/scaffolding/gssjc/news"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="GSSJC announces September Gold Award recipients"
        jcr:uuid="88f20fdb-50c3-4a8f-b4bf-e01dc7a8e0da"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/news-page"
        date="{Date}2014-09-30T09:53:59.000-05:00"
        description="Four southeast Texas Girl Scouts from San Jacinto Council recently earned Girl Scouts of the USA’s Gold Award, the highest award a Girl Scout can receive. Less than five percent of girls who join Girl Scouts achieve this national recognition. Girl Scouts Hannah S. of Spring, Julie S. of Cy-Fair, Srini S. of Katy and Jennifer J. of Katy each earned the award.">
        <middle jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <par jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                <text
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="foundation/components/textimage"
                    text="&lt;p>Four southeast Texas Girl Scouts from San Jacinto Council recently earned Girl Scouts of the USA’s Gold Award, the highest award a Girl Scout can receive. Less than five percent of girls who join Girl Scouts achieve this national recognition. Girl Scouts Hannah S. of Spring, Julie S. of Cy-Fair, Srini S. of Katy and Jennifer J. of Katy each earned the award.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The Girl Scout Gold Award represents the highest achievement in Girl Scouting; it recognizes girls in grades 9 through 12 who demonstrate extraordinary leadership through sustainable and measurable Take Action projects. Since 1916, girls have successfully answered the call to Go Gold, an act that indelibly marks them as accomplished members of their communities and the world.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Hannah S. renovated a visitation room at Child Protective Services to earn the Gold Award. For her project, Hannah visited with local business to ask for furniture donations. Once the donations were secured, she led a team of volunteers in renovating the room from top to bottom. Hannah repainted the walls and created a book nook for children to enjoy. She also moved in furniture, toys and installed a TV with a DVD player. She hoped to make the room more inviting to families.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Julie S. established a drama club for children and Boys and Girls Country in Hockley, TX to earn the Gold Award. Julie met with officials at Boys and Girls Country to pitch her idea. Once approved, she developed curriculum for a weekly club meeting where she taught students the basics of writing plays, acting and theater production. The club met for four months, and at the end of the year they performed a play at Boys and Girls Country’s Spring Festival.&lt;br>&#xa; &lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Srini S. created hygiene kits, wrote a book and directed a short video on good hygiene for children at Ekal Vidyalaya, a nonprofit organization benefitting children in rural India, to earn the Gold Award. First, Srini collected toiletries to put together hygiene kits for children. Second, she researched and authored a book on good hygiene geared towards children and translated her book into Gujarati and Hindi. Finally, she wrote, directed and edited a video – also in Gujarati and Hindi – designed to teach children good hygiene skills. Everything created and collected was donated to Ekal Vidyalaya, a nonprofit involved in education and village development in rural India.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Jennifer J. wrote a cookbook for diabetics using commonly available ingredients to earn the Gold Award. She researched and tested recipes for diabetics that she wanted to include in her book. Her recipes focused on using ingredients most common to households or easy to find ingredients. She also sought out healthy recipes. Once she finalized the list of recipes, Jennifer compiled them into a cookbook and delivered physical and electronic copies to Katy Christian Ministries’ food pantry and to the nutritionist at the Houston Food Bank. Both organizations agreed to pass on copies to their current diabetic clients and can use it as a resource for years to come.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>For more information on the Gold Award, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.girlscouts.org/goldaward&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>girlscouts.org/goldaward&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                    textIsRich="true">
                    <image
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-10-06T10:54:55.448-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="menzor"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                        fileReference="/content/dam/gssjc/news-images/go-gold.jpg"
                        imageRotate="0"/>
                </text>
            </par>
        </middle>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
