<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2016-01-06T14:06:36.317-05:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
        cq:scaffolding="/etc/scaffolding/gateway/event"
        cq:tags="[gateway:categories/girl-events]"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Girl Scouts Super Science Saturday- All &amp; PA"
        jcr:uuid="843e25fe-c0ea-4b93-9f89-040ed9d57d79"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/event-page">
        <data
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            address="904 S Main St, Gainesville, FL 32601"
            color="#EC008C"
            details="&lt;p>Girl Scouts Super Science Saturday- ALL&lt;br>&#xa;Grades: K, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Are you ready to roll up your sleeves and try new things? Full “S.T.E.A.M.” ahead as we dive into the fun at the Cade Labs. From creating exothermic reactions and trying your hand on a 3D doodler Pen, to making a spectroscopy scope and a sound wave amplification device, you are sure to find something fun to do! Interested in engineering?&amp;nbsp; Learn up close about the interesting career paths studying engineering can take you.&amp;nbsp; This is your chance to meet and make, design and fabricate all in one fun filled day!&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Are you a trained PA? Then, this event is for you, too! The Cade Museum would love your help running the different stations. You will arrive 1 hour and a half early to learn your station and receive 4.5 volunteer hours for participating.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;The Cade Museum welcomes everyone to bring along a sack lunch and find a nice spot on the property to picnic after the program is complete. This is encouraged, but not mandatory. Fun patch and Cade Lab loot bag included.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;*This event is for PA’s and Girl Scouts. Please select which level you are during registration.&lt;br>&#xa;*For safety and supervision reasons, troops and individuals are not permitted to bring non-Girl Scouts or siblings.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;*Girl/adult ratios must be followed and adults are expected to stay on the premises during the event.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;$20/girl, $1/adult&lt;br>&#xa;Contact: Brittany McCallister 904.389.3071&lt;/p>&#xa;"
            end="{Date}2016-04-16T12:00:00.000-04:00"
            locationLabel="Cade Museum for Creativity &amp; Invention"
            register="http://girlscouts-gateway.doubleknot.com/event/girl-scouts-super-science-saturday-all-pa/1826647"
            start="{Date}2016-04-16T09:00:00.012-04:00">
            <image
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2016-01-06T14:06:36.310-05:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                fileReference="/content/dam/gateway/pageImgs/Council Program Event.png"
                imageRotate="0"/>
        </data>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
