<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2014-08-01T11:06:58.012-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="mkaufman"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2014-08-01T11:07:10.756-04:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="mkaufman"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:scaffolding="/etc/scaffolding/gateway/news"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Comcast Donation Helps North Florida Girl Scouts Get Connected"
        jcr:uuid="6e8bc5a9-53e0-4ab2-ba55-1c503a40a037"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/news-page"
        date="{Date}2014-07-22T11:06:54.000-04:00">
        <middle jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <par jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                <text
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="foundation/components/textimage"
                    text="&lt;p>&lt;b>JACKSONVILLE, FLA – July 22 2014 – &lt;/b>A local nonprofit organization is better equipped to train its members and volunteers after a donation from Comcast. The Girl Scouts of the Gateway Council received ten netbook computers and free Comcast services, including high speed internet and cable television.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>“We’ve been serving girls in Northeast Florida since the early 1920’s. Technology has changed a bit over the decades.&amp;nbsp; The generous gift of high speed internet access and ten Acer Netbooks from Comcast will enable the Girl Scouts of the Gateway Council to train girls and adult volunteers, “ said the Girl Scouts of Gateway Council CEO Mary Anne Jacobs. “Not all of our Girl Scouts and adult volunteers have access to high-speed internet.&amp;nbsp; Almost everything we do is moving into a robust digital environment.&amp;nbsp; Comcast’s donation will provide Girl Scouts access to the information girls need to be ready for college and a globally competitive workplace.”&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>“Comcast is proud to support the great work of the members and volunteers of the Girl Scouts of the Gateway Council through this donation,” said Bill Ferry, Comcast North Florida Senior Director, Government and Regulatory Affairs &amp;amp; Community Investment. “Comcast is committed to giving back to organizations like the Girl Scouts in all of the communities we serve.”&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Girl Scouts of Gateway Council, Inc. is a registered 501C (3) organization with membership open to all girls in kindergarten through 12th grade. With offices in Jacksonville, Gainesville, and Middleburg, Girl Scouts of Gateway Council, Inc., services over 18,000 girls and adults in 16 North Florida counties – from the Gulf of Mexico to the Atlantic Ocean.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Photo Caption: &lt;/b>At left, Mary Anne Jacobs, CEO of the Girl Scouts of the Gateway Council and Bill Ferry, Comcast North Florida Senior Director, Government and Regulatory Affairs &amp;amp; Community Investment, with the ten netbook computers Comcast donated to the nonprofit organization along with services including high speed internet and cable television.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>About Comcast Corporation&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.comcastcorporation.com/&quot;>Comcast Corporation&lt;/a> (Nasdaq: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cmcsa.com/&quot;>CMCSA&lt;/a>, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cmcsk.com/&quot;>CMCSK&lt;/a>) is a global media and technology company with two primary businesses, Comcast Cable and NBCUniversal.&amp;nbsp; Comcast Cable is the nation's largest video, high-speed Internet and phone provider to residential customers under the XFINITY brand and also provides these services to businesses.&amp;nbsp; NBCUniversal operates 30 news, entertainment and sports cable networks, the NBC and Telemundo broadcast networks, television production operations, television station groups, Universal Pictures and Universal Parks and Resorts.&amp;nbsp; Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.comcastcorporation.com/&quot;>www.comcastcorporation.com&lt;/a> for more information.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                    textIsRich="true">
                    <image
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-08-01T11:06:58.008-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="mkaufman"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                        fileReference="/content/dam/gateway/cropped feature_story2.jpg"
                        imageRotate="0"/>
                </text>
            </par>
        </middle>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
