<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2014-10-29T16:18:23.924-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="bmoore"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2014-10-29T16:18:30.019-04:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="bmoore"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:scaffolding="/etc/scaffolding/gateway/event"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Basic Troop Camp Certification"
        jcr:uuid="0a5b006b-0426-40f8-8d76-7079d1531210"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/event-page">
        <data
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            address="697 SW Baya Drive, Lake City, FL"
            details="&lt;p>Girl Scouts of Gateway Council Basic Troop Camp Certification allows you to take your girls camping practically anywhere! Anyone in the troop/group can be the camp-trained volunteer. When you sign up for Session II and III, you must be able to attend both of these sessions together, as the in-town is the planning session for the camp session.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>In order to be certified for this course, participants must complete all three of the stages:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Basic Troop Camp Certification Session I (CD):&lt;/b> This portion will review:&amp;nbsp; Planning with your girls, Kaper Charts, Progression, Outdoor Skills, and more!&amp;nbsp; Please contact the Service Center (904-388-4653)&amp;nbsp;to receive a disc.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Basic Troop Camp Certification Session II (In-town):&lt;/b> This class will be an opportunity to get together a team and work with other volunteers and plan your meals for the camp session.&amp;nbsp; This is the in-town session that prepares you for Session III.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Basic Troop Camp Certification Session III (Overnight):&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b> Utilize the planning that you and your patrol developed during your in-town training session at camp.&amp;nbsp; In the final step of this process, volunteers attend camp to participate and demonstrate the skills that they have learned under the careful instruction of a facilitator.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; This session has been developed to meet the needs of all of our volunteers.&amp;nbsp; If you are a hearty camper who has slept in the out-of-doors in a cabin or tent, you will only need to attend this class for the day on Saturday. For those volunteers who have never camped or are uncomfortable with the out-of-doors, you will begin your at-camp session on Friday evening and experience the adventure of sleeping in the out-of-doors.&amp;nbsp; Discussion with your facilitator during the in-town camp portion will decide which opportunity is best for you.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Registering for this session&amp;nbsp;registers you for all three sessions&lt;/p>&#xa;"
            end="{Date}2014-11-06T21:00:00.000-05:00"
            locationLabel="First Presbyterian Church Lake City"
            register="https://gsusa.ebiz.uapps.net/vp/FamilyManagement/ProductDetail.aspx?ProductId=847228685"
            start="{Date}2014-11-06T18:00:00.000-05:00">
            <image
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-10-29T16:18:23.918-04:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="bmoore"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                imageRotate="0"/>
        </data>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
