<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2015-12-08T11:52:31.560-05:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
        cq:tags="[gateway:categories/camp]"
        cq:template="/apps/girlscouts/templates/three-column-page"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Summer Resident Camps"
        jcr:uuid="b9c2d424-96ff-408a-a39d-18b83d5262a8"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/three-column-page"
        seoTitle="Summer Resident Camps | Girl Scouts of Gateway Council">
        <content jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <middle jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                <par
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="foundation/components/parsys">
                    <image
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-06-24T14:17:05.894-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="ctruett"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-02-23T14:52:34.721-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="bmoore"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/image"
                        fileReference="/content/dam/gateway/pageImgs/camp1.png"
                        imageRotate="0"/>
                    <title
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-06-10T13:42:49.138-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="mkaufman"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-06-10T13:42:49.138-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="mkaufman"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/title"/>
                    <text
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-06-10T13:51:06.798-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="mkaufman"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-12-08T11:52:31.557-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Stay tuned for Camp Kateri 2016!&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Your summer adventure at Camp Kateri will be here before you know it! Discover the leader in you as you support and encourage your fellow campers to do the same. Enriching activities like camping, hiking, canoeing, singing, dancing, art, challenging games and natural exploration will set the most exciting backdrop for you to explore, identify and honor the unique set of skills and qualities that make you, you. Celebrate the new talents, interests and friends you discover at camp that will last a lifetime.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>The Camp&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Camp Kateri is a 550-acre facility located just 30 minutes southeast of Gainesville, Florida. Camp Kateri has offered fun-filled programs for 50 years, in which campers not only get to experience new adventures, but also grow in their personal skills. Camp Kateri is a sleep-away camp with weeklong sessions beginning on Sunday and ending on Friday. During their stay at Camp Kateri, girls live in cabins, platform tents and treehouses. Each unit has flush toilets, running water and electricity in the unit houses. Camp Kateri is owned and operated by the Girl Scouts of Gateway Council, Inc.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;i>“Thank you for providing a camp that helps build my daughter's self-esteem, confidence and challenges her. Also, thank you for finding delightful young ladies to work as counselors that model appropriate behavior my daughter can strive to emulate. We will definitely be returning to Camp Kateri next year.”&lt;/i> –Parent of a 2013 Camper&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>The Staff &lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Campers will spend their days with fun-loving, safety-conscious camp staff. For many girls, there is nothing better than getting to know these young adults—role models who are confident enough to dress up and sing silly songs, who can mediate a dispute, who can make such an impression that they are remembered 20 years later. All staff are trained in First Aid, CPR, counseling, emergency procedures, and more.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>If you or someone you know loves to work with Girl Scouts in an outdoor environment, we will be accepting applications beginning in January 2016 for our Summer 2016 season.&amp;nbsp; All positions have certain requirements you must meet to be hired.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Camp Kateri Sessions&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Camp Kateri Resident Camp runs for six weeks during the summer. Each session is themed and all activities throughout the day are age appropriate with the goal of each girl discovering who they are, connecting with others and taking action to make the world a better place, all while having fun outdoors. The sessions begin on Sunday afternoon and end Friday morning.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </par>
            </middle>
        </content>
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-04-06T14:45:07.305-04:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="drodgers"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            imageRotate="0"/>
    </jcr:content>
    <camp-activities/>
    <food-service/>
    <sumCampJobs/>
    <cit/>
    <specProg/>
    <readyforcamp/>
    <Camp_Kateri_map/>
</jcr:root>
