<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2015-06-29T12:18:02.653-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2015-06-29T12:18:16.169-04:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="dpage"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:scaffolding="/etc/scaffolding/gateway/news"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Five Gainesville women honored for community leadership and service"
        jcr:uuid="1c955831-7535-4880-9d80-c1ab86034561"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/news-page"
        date="{Date}2015-04-29T12:13:00.000-04:00"
        external-url="http://www.gainesville.com/article/20150514/ARTICLES/150519809/0/search">
        <middle jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <par jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                <text
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/textimage"
                    text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Gainesville, Fla.&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp;– The Girl Scouts of Gateway Council pays tribute to five of Gainesville’s most accomplished women whose professional achievements and community service have made lasting impacts to the Gainesville area. Area business and civic leaders will join Girl Scouts of Gateway Council on May 14 at the Women Who Make A Difference luncheon to honor the contributions of Jane Adams, vice president of University Relations for University of Florida; Karen Harris, M.D., M.P.H., president of North Florida Women’s Physicians of Gainesville; Brittany Lee, vice president of Florida Blue Farms, Inc.; Shaney Livingston, director of the Alachua County Library District; and Jane Muir, associate director of the Office of Technology Licensing for University of Florida, director of UF Tech Connect and director of the Florida Innovation Hub at UF. The event will be held at the Hilton UF Conference Center from 11:30 a.m. – 1:00 p.m.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>“These extraordinary women demonstrate leadership and stewardship for all, but most importantly, for today’s Girl Scouts, who are our future leaders,” said Mary Anne Jacobs, chief executive officer of Girl Scouts of Gateway Council. “Brittany, Shaney, Karen, Jane Muir and Jane Adams are real-life role models our girls can learn from and emulate as they grow into confident young women capable of making positive changes in their communities and the world.”&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The dedication, vision and talents of the five honorees have far-reaching impacts on business, education, medicine, youth mentoring, health, women’s leadership and beyond.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Honorees are selected by volunteers, Council staff and a member of the Council’s board of directors. Proceeds from “Women Who Make a Difference” support the Girl Scout leadership program for area girls.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                    textIsRich="true">
                    <image
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-06-29T12:18:02.646-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                        imageRotate="0"/>
                </text>
            </par>
        </middle>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
