<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2014-06-05T19:44:57.060-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="admin"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2014-06-06T15:42:18.225-04:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="admin"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:scaffolding="/etc/scaffolding/girlscouts-usa/event"
        cq:tags="[]"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Wilderness First Aid"
        jcr:uuid="abff2f18-0ed0-4127-bda7-315fe62d3df5"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/event-page">
        <data
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            details="&lt;p>Wilderness First Aid (WFA) training is for wildress environments where advanced medical care may be significantly delayed. The term &amp;quot;remote&amp;quot; is sometimes added and implies the possiability of care delay in other evironments such as during a natural disaster in an urban area. GSUSA rewuires WFA certified volunteers for activies where EMS may be significantly delayed.&amp;nbsp; This is an Emergency Care and Saftey Insitute (ECSI) class in association with the American Academy of Orthopedic Surgeons and the American College of Emergency Physicians. Certification is vaild for two years. This class is open to adult leaders. Mature youth age 18 or older who have been approved by their unit leader may also participate. All registrants must be currently registered members. Adults need to have completed the background check prior to training. Current CPR/AED certification is mandatory. WFA is not simply &amp;quot;advanced first aid.&amp;quot; This course is thought provoking and will test the ability to gather and synthesize pertinent information quickly and accurately, make difficult decisions regarding scope of practice, and weigh risk versus potential benefit in an austere setting. Each participant will be a team leader in a wilderness mass casualty scenario, devise evacuation and patient movement plans. and facilitate transfer to higher care using standardized documentation. The class is a fast paced, non-flexiable 16-hour curriculm. Students participate in skills practice, group activities, and scenarios. Lectures and demonstrations will continue through lunch periods. Scenarios will take place outdoors regarless of weather and will include patient drags and carries. Participants must attend both daily sessions. Class is held 8:00 a.m.-6:00 p.m., Saturday, June 14, 2014. The other portion is held 8:00 a.m.- 3:00 p.m., Sunday, June 15, 2014.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a href=&quot;https://gsusa.ebiz.uapps.net/vp/default.aspx?pid=7&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Register This Event&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;"
            end="{Date}2014-06-15T15:00:00.000-04:00"
            locationLabel="Richlands Scout Hut- Onslow County"
            srchdisp="Wilderness First Aid (WFA) training is for wilderness environments where advanced medical care may be significantly delayed. "
            start="{Date}2014-06-14T08:00:00.000-04:00">
            <image
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-06-05T19:44:57.054-04:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                fileReference="/content/dam/girlscouts-shared/en/upcoming_events"
                imageRotate="0"/>
        </data>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
