<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2015-04-06T14:45:32.066-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="drodgers"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2014-07-30T01:50:06.939-04:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="mzou"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[gateway:categories/camp]"
        cq:template="/apps/girlscouts/templates/three-column-page"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Camp Activities"
        jcr:uuid="e70e5ea8-2d10-4171-9fc3-b9c683f6915c"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/three-column-page"
        seoTitle="Camp Activities | Girl Scouts of Gateway Council">
        <content jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <middle jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                <par
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="foundation/components/parsys">
                    <image
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-07-17T14:20:32.821-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="ctruett"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-07-17T14:20:43.523-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="ctruett"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/image"
                        fileReference="/content/dam/gateway/pageheroes/hero_activities.jpg"/>
                    <title
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-06-10T13:43:01.583-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="mkaufman"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-06-10T13:43:01.583-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="mkaufman"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/title"/>
                    <text
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-06-10T13:47:20.264-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="mkaufman"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-07-18T14:47:56.308-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="ctruett"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>For Summer Resident Camp&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Girls participate in fun, educational and developmental activities at Camp Kateri. Many are specific to the session as described in the camp brochure and on the website, while others are chosen by the campers after they arrive. It is the goal of all activities at camp to build girls of courage, confidence and character who make the world a better place.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h4>Main Programs&lt;/h4>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Archery&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Campers love learning to shoot like Robin Hood at our six-lane covered archery range.&amp;nbsp; Girls have the opportunity to learn proper technique and play fun games, including tic-tac-toe and balloon pop!&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Canoeing and Kayaking&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Water enthusiasts have a great time at our waterfront! Once campers have mastered paddling techniques, our small-craft instructors turn the fun up even higher with relays, floating lunches and more!&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Sailing&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Campers feel the wind in their sails (and their hair) as they sail across Lake McCarthy with a friend. Our fleet consists of prams for beginners and Lasers for more advanced sailors.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>STEM&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Girls are naturally curious. What better place than camp to answer some of the questions they have about Science, Technology, Engineering and Math. Girls will try new experiments, learn about the forces of nature and work as a team to solve problems.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Swimming&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;A favorite! After taking a swim test, campers get to cool off in the lake and play water games. On the beach, they can build castles before heading back to the water!&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Barn Visits&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Girls who aren’t in an equestrian program can visit the barn to meet the horses (and maybe even give them treats)! The equestrian staff gives tours and answers questions to satisfy campers’ love of all things equine.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Arts and Crafts&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Crafts are a favorite camp pastime. Our most popular activities include making lanyards, tie-dying, and painting. Girls love relaxing and chatting as they work on their masterpieces.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Night Hikes&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Campers love to stay up late—and they love to hike in the dark. As their eyes adjust, girls see familiar surroundings differently and learn to listen to the sounds of nature. Fireflies and stars are frequent companions!&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </par>
            </middle>
        </content>
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-04-06T14:45:32.060-04:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="drodgers"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            imageRotate="0"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
