<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-05T15:33:26.098-05:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
        cq:scaffolding="/etc/scaffolding/gateway/event"
        cq:tags="[gateway:categories/girl-events]"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Astronomy Solar- JCSA"
        jcr:uuid="40a8acca-31f1-40d9-90cc-1df4d2e672b9"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/event-page">
        <data
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            color="#EC008C"
            details="&lt;p>The sun will come out tomorrow with our sun course! Girl Scouts will be able to see our sun safely through telescopes during this session. Plus- we are going to experiment with a new model demonstrating how mass of stars, like the sun, plays a role in the space-time continuum around the stars! Are you a PA? Then this event is for you, too! PA’s will be able to increase their astronomical knowledge and have some fun helping our younger Girl Scouts discover the mysteries of the sky above! Safe use of the telescopes will be emphasized. Add some layers today because it may get chilly!&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>$7/Girl Scout, $7/adult, no fee for PA's&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>*This event is for PA’s and Girl Scouts. Please select which level you are during registration&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>*A fun patch is provided with this program!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>*Telescopic viewing of the Sun weather permitting.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>** All attendees must be registered Girl Scouts for the 2016 Membership Year.&amp;nbsp; All adults must be registered and approved volunteers.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>** Chaperones must stay on property during the event and are encouraged to participate.&amp;nbsp; Please see Safety Activity checkpoints for ratios&lt;/p>&#xa;"
            end="{Date}2015-12-05T17:00:00.000-05:00"
            locationLabel="North Fork"
            register="http://girlscouts-gateway.doubleknot.com/OpenRosters/ViewActivitySpaceAvailable.aspx?classificationID=38127&amp;sf=F&amp;orgkey=2736%20"
            start="{Date}2015-12-05T14:00:00.012-05:00">
            <image
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-05T15:33:26.093-05:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                fileReference="/content/dam/gateway/images/AstronomySolarpatch.jpeg"
                imageRotate="0"/>
        </data>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
