<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2014-09-11T17:28:34.717-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="mtolbert"
        cq:scaffolding="/etc/scaffolding/gssjc/news"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Lufkin Middle School uses Girl Scout BFF Program to help prevent bullying"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/news-page"
        date="{Date}2014-08-14T16:07:00.000-05:00">
        <middle jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <par jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                <text
                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-09-11T17:28:34.715-04:00"
                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="mtolbert"
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="foundation/components/text"
                    text="&lt;p>Lukfin Middle School integrated program curriculum provided by Girl Scouts of the U.S.A to raise awareness about bullying prevention in its Health and Physical Education classes. The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.girlscouts.org/program/journeys/bff/default.asp?utm_campaign=vanityurl&amp;amp;utm_medium=girlscouts.org&amp;amp;utm_source=bff&quot;>Be a Friend First (BFF)&lt;/a> program, designed to work with the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.girlscouts.org/program/journeys/your_world/cadette.asp&quot;>aMAZE Journey&lt;/a>, a program designed for middle school-aged Girl Scouts that guides them through the twists and turns of pre-adolescence to find true friendship and build confidence, gives girls valuable skills to develop healthy relationships, prevent bullying and become peacemakers in their schools.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;“The topics featured in the aMAZE Journey are definitely part of these girls’ day-to-day lives, especially in middle school,” said Sharon Means, Lukfin Middle School Health and Physical Education teacher.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Through a United Way grant and assistance from 10 students from Stephen F. Austin (SFA) University in Nacogdoches, who led all of the program sessions, more than 50 middle school students were engaged in BFF. Since the volunteers were closer in age to the students, the pre-teens felt more comfortable opening up about their experiences. The SFA students completed Volunteer Essentials training, a requirement for adults serving as Girl Scout volunteers. The United Way grant was used to provide program materials for the sessions and paid for the students’ Girl Scout membership.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;“BFF really gave the girls a chance to get out of their shells and opened their eyes to a program that could benefit them in more than just a social way,” said Alexandra Andrews, an SFA student and former Girl Scout who helped facilitate the BFF program at Lufkin Middle School. “I would love to do this in other schools and since I moved back home to Houston to do my student teaching, I was hoping I would be able to find another school that was implementing the BFF program.”&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;As part of the BFF program, girls explore thorny issues like peer pressure, stereotyping, gossip, and cliques through engaging role-plays, creative writing, games, and discussion exercises. They can also create and lead projects in their schools and communities to tackle bullying issues on their terms and turf. BFF easily integrates into existing health or character education classes or can serve as an after-school program in the community. Means understands that healthy relationships are the solution to bully prevention and the BFF program inspires girls to lead one another—with friendship.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;“The aMAZE Journey was so engaging and my health students seemed to really enjoy some of the messages and activities,” said Means. “I cover a chapter regarding relationships and social health and I felt that the information and activities the program offered were very beneficial and fit right into my curriculum.”&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;GSSJC is making its summer push for girls and adult volunteers to join Girl Scouts, the country’s preeminent leadership development organization for girls.&amp;nbsp; For more information about Girl Scouts in the Lufkin area, contact Christopher Robuck at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:crobuck@sjgs.org&quot;>crobuck@sjgs.org&lt;/a> or call 936-634-5813.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Girl Scouts of the USA is the world's preeminent organization for girls, with a membership of more than 3.2 million girls and adults. Girl Scouting builds girls of courage, confidence, and character, who make the world a better place. Chartered by GSUSA to provide Girl Scouting locally, Girl Scouts of San Jacinto Council is one of the largest Girl Scout councils in the country serving approximately 63,000 girls and nearly 19,000 adult members in 26 southeast Texas counties.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                    textIsRich="true">
                    <image
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-09-11T17:27:37.199-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="mtolbert"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        jcr:title="Girl Scouts in red life vests standing infront of canoe rack."
                        sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                        imageRotate="0">
                        <file/>
                    </image>
                </text>
            </par>
        </middle>
    </jcr:content>
    <_x0032_014/>
</jcr:root>
