<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2015-01-09T11:28:15.126-05:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="bmoore"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2015-01-09T11:28:34.070-05:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="bmoore"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:scaffolding="/etc/scaffolding/gateway/event"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Basic Troop Camp Training"
        jcr:uuid="06020d83-dcab-4452-a196-7c8459b74ea5"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/event-page">
        <data
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            details="&lt;p>Girl Scouts of Gateway Council’s Basic Troop Camp Certification (3 sessions) enables you to provide an amazing outdoor adventure for your girls.&amp;nbsp; Any of the registered Volunteers within a Troop may be designated as the Troop Outdoor Coordinator and complete this training.&amp;nbsp; Please note that you must complete all 3 sessions to receive your Basic Troop Camp Certification.&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;b>Session 1 (Self-Guided):&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp; You will be introduced to the basics of camping, from preparing your girls for the outdoor experience, to planning and budgeting for the overnight trip.&amp;nbsp; You will learn about important safety procedures and council policies involved with making your trip a success.&amp;nbsp; Instructions regarding the online Self-Guided material will be emailed once your registration for this training is finalized.&amp;nbsp; Important Note:&amp;nbsp;&lt;b> The Self-Guided session will need to be completed prior to your In-Town session.&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;b>Session 2 (In-Town):&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp; This fun and interactive session will further complement the skills you have developed by allowing you to work closely with a camp trained individual who will ensure that you have everything you need to properly camp in the outdoors.&amp;nbsp; This In-Town session is a planning workshop designed specifically for your overnight adventure.&amp;nbsp; Your facilitator will guide you through a unique and wonderful camping experience!&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;b>Date: Tues.&amp;nbsp; Jan 13, 2015; 6:00 PM - 8:00 PM&lt;br>&#xa;Location: Palatka Little House&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;b>Session 3 (Overnight):&lt;/b> This exciting overnight session will complete your camping certification.&amp;nbsp; You will utilize the skills developed during your previous sessions to further understand the outdoor experience.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;b>Date: Fri. Jan 23, 2015; 6:00 PM – Sat. Jan 24, 2015, 6:00 PM&lt;br>&#xa;Location: Camp Kateri-Lilly Pad&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;Last day to register online is Jan. 11, 2015.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;"
            end="{Date}2015-01-13T20:00:00.000-05:00"
            locationLabel="Palatka Little House"
            register="https://gsusa.ebiz.uapps.net/vp/FamilyManagement/ProductDetail.aspx?ProductId=1275778093"
            srchdisp="Girl Scouts of Gateway Council’s Basic Troop Camp Certification enables you to provide an amazing outdoor adventure for your girls! "
            start="{Date}2015-01-13T18:00:00.008-05:00">
            <image
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-01-09T11:28:15.121-05:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="bmoore"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                imageRotate="0"/>
        </data>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
