<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2015-10-02T08:50:36.850-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
        cq:scaffolding="/etc/scaffolding/gateway/event"
        cq:tags="[gateway:categories/volunteer]"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Community 6 JOTI 2015 "
        jcr:uuid="851c1c39-376f-4bb3-a7b1-77a717933597"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/event-page">
        <data
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            color="#AB218E"
            details="&lt;p>Jamboree on the Internet (JOTI), is&amp;nbsp;a worldwide scouting activity that has Girl Scouts&amp;nbsp;and Boy Scouts across the globe talking to each other via Skype. Sharing experiences, information about scouting in different countries, seeing each other’s uniforms etc.&amp;nbsp; The girls will get to talk to all four Girl Scout houses -Mexico, India, England, and Switzerland.&amp;nbsp; Girls participating will receive a patch.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>JOTI stations will be throughout Gateway Council, location and shift specifics will be sent out once registration is complete.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>** all participants must be registered Girl Scouts for the 2016 Membership year.&amp;nbsp; All adults attending this session must be registered approved volunteers and adhere to Safety Activity Checkpoint ratios.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Last day to register: 10 October 2015&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>JOTI 2015 (Jamboree on the Internet)&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Guidelines and Instructions&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>JOTI is typically held over the third weekend in October each year. Scouts from all over the world communicate with each other via Amateur Radio Ham Operators and the Internet. The Girl Scouts of Gateway Council has elected to join in the world event via SKYPE (Free). &lt;b>&lt;i>The world event starts at 0:01am Saturday October 17th through to 11:59pm on October 18&lt;sup>th&lt;/sup>, 2015.&lt;/i>&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>There are two methods in which your Girl Scouts may participate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>(a) Establish a Community Group and invite the local community scouts to join you at a local public facility (Libraries, YMCA, Church Halls, etc.) or designate a home that has internet capability and operate your own exclusive JOTI station.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Leaders interested in leading such a combined community group with a number of troops, need to make their own arrangements to facilitate the groups and facilities. Depending on the facilities operating hours, you may find that you are limited to operate your JOTI station during their normal hours of business. See the list of equipment and items that you will need below.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>(b) Establish a smaller group or troop gathering at a scouts home that has internet activity.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>This option offers the flexibilty of operating during any hours of the weekend. Remember when the American scouts are operating, most European, Asian and African countries are asleep. A home site will also give you the flexibility to start and stop your Skype communications when you want. You can choose your time to catch the international scouts when they are active. See the list of equipment and items that you will need below.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>JOTI Stations:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>John Van Zyl has created a number of pre-loaded JOTI station accounts for each community. Seven community group names will be created for the event, with a number of additional sub-stations. Contact addresses and pass codes will be alloacted to interetsed leaders for their groups and/or troops. All leaders planning to operate group or individual stations, must register their intention to do so with John, no later that October 9&lt;sup>th&lt;/sup>. Email your requests to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:johnvanzyl@comcast.net&quot;>johnvanzyl@comcast.net&lt;/a>. John will require the leaders to provide: (i) Name of the community group or troop, (ii) Name of responsible leader that will monitor the JOTI station, (iii) Contact phone number, (iv) Email address.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Late requests may not be accepted and your girls will be dissapointed that they could not participate. It takes time to setup the stations and preload the 150-200 international scout stations. Before each contact can be used during JOTI, each contact has to receive and accept your JOTI stations skype request. Some countries take time to respond to requests and you may miss the opportunity to chat with that country. If your scouts want to chat with Asia, Africa, Astralia, India and the Pacific rim countries, you may want to arrange a sleepover and/or lockin to have the girls stay up during the late hours to catch these countries while they are operating. The pre-loaded contacts have been screened and appear to all be legitimate scouting contacts. We have encouraged all international scout leaders that will be managing the Skype groups to involve a number of girl and boy scouts on each JOTI chat sessions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>What is the cost of the event?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>$5.00 per scout prticipating. This cost will go towards special event patches, facility costs and refreshments at the larger group event locations.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>What equipment and items do you require to establish your group or troop JOTI station?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ol>&#xa;&lt;li>1. Have parents loan the group or troop newer laptops with internet capability for the event. The larger the group, the more laptops and monitors you will require. &lt;i>A manageable size group is between 4-6 scouts on a single JOTI session.&lt;/i>&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>2. It is recommended that larger monitors also be hooked up to the laptops, to enable a larger group to join in the conversation.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>3. A large table or desk with 4-6 chairs for each station&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>4. Internet, WiFi and router capability or cable connected to a high speed and broad band router.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>5. Scouts neatly dressed in uniform (Vest or sash). &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>6. Leader to monitor and facilitate communications and topics of discussion.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ol>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Internet Safety Tips and Guidelines.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>a. Always have a leader in the room during all skype sessions.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>b. Monitor topics of discussions.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ol>&#xa;&lt;li>c. Never have the girls share personal information such as Facebook accounts and home addresses. If the scouts want to trade patches or scout memrabilia after the event, have the leader take down the international addresses. Some international scouts enjoy swapping or trading patches with the USA scouts.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>d. Leaders are to terminate any unacceptable communications. Report the event and skype account immediately to &lt;i>Beachesgirlscouts1&lt;/i>, this will allow us to remove that account from all operating JOTI stations in the Gateway Council.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ol>&#xa;&lt;p>Community 6 Waters Edge is inviting all communities to join at the following&amp;nbsp;group&amp;nbsp;event locations on October 17, 2015.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Christ's Church Mandarin (6045 Greenland Rd. Jacksonville, FL 322580) in dining hall from 9:00am - 1:00pm&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Pablo Creek Library&amp;nbsp;(&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bing.com/maps/default.aspx?cp=30.28761~-81.47326&amp;amp;where1=Pablo%20Creek%20Library&amp;amp;ss=ypid.YN178x3332373&amp;amp;FORM=SNAPST&quot;>13295 Beach Blvd, Jacksonville, FL 32246&lt;/a>)&amp;nbsp;in room B from 3:30pm - 6:00pm&lt;/p>&#xa;"
            end="{Date}2015-10-18T17:00:00.000-04:00"
            locationLabel="Skype"
            register="http://girlscouts-gateway.doubleknot.com/openrosters/ViewActivitySpaceAvailable.aspx?orgkey=2736&amp;activitykey=1784782"
            start="{Date}2015-10-17T08:00:00.132-04:00">
            <image
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-10-02T08:50:36.845-04:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                fileReference="/content/dam/gateway/images/SC130221 A.jpg"
                imageRotate="0"/>
        </data>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
