<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2014-10-07T14:48:44.791-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="mtolbert"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2014-10-07T14:48:50.495-04:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="mtolbert"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:scaffolding="/etc/scaffolding/gssjc/news"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Port Arthur volunteers say Girl Scouts is good way to give back to community"
        jcr:uuid="68a8fc5e-8dd3-4cff-be6c-bdf42b3a661c"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/news-page"
        date="{Date}2014-10-07T10:58:00.000-05:00"
        description="Port Arthur volunteers Yolonda Stevenson and Diane Dennis, troop leaders of a multi-level troop with more than 25 girls, are passionate about Girl Scouts and know it gives girls opportunities that they would not have – getting involved in their communities, learning new skills and growing to become their best selves. ">
        <middle jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <par jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                <text
                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-10-07T14:48:44.789-04:00"
                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="mtolbert"
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="foundation/components/text"
                    text="&lt;p>From its beginnings, Girl Scouts has taught girls that they can make a difference in their communities. It has also given adults the opportunity to give back by serving as mentors, helping girls to maximize their potential so that they can achieve their goals.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Port Arthur volunteers Yolonda Stevenson and Diane Dennis, troop leaders of a multi-level troop with more than 25 girls, are passionate about Girl Scouts and know it gives girls opportunities that they would not have – getting involved in their communities, learning new skills and growing to become their best selves.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Troop #3686 was established in 2013 with only six Girl Scouts. Since then, it has grown and accommodated every request for girls seeking troops in Port Arthur and surrounding areas.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>“We will continue taking girls until we can’t take anymore because we don’t want to see any girls without a troop,” said Dennis.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Stevenson and Dennis’ troop consists of girls in each of the six Girl Scout levels – Daisy, Brownie, Junior, Cadette, Senior and Ambassador – and they have no plans to split the troop. Typically, troops are comprised of girls of the same age in the same Girl Scout level. However, the volunteers decided to keep the troop multi-leveled at the request of the girls’ parents.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>“Many of the parents have more than one daughter in Girl Scouts, so keeping their daughters in the same troop cuts down on the number of times they have to get their daughters to meetings or events,” said Stevenson. “Sometimes if parents have to go out several times, the girls may not show up.”&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Keeping the troop multi-leveled not only helps the parents but also the volunteers. Stevenson, who lives in Baytown, commutes to Port Arthur during the week for troop meetings and special events. The troop currently has three leaders and four co-leaders, and many of them participated in Girl Scouts as girls and know firsthand that the values girls learn as members of the organization will take them through adulthood.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>This Girl Scout year, Troop #3686 volunteers are looking forward to helping some of their Girl Scouts earn their First Aid badge and the Bronze and Silver Awards, the highest honors a Girl Scout Junior and Cadette can achieve, respectively. The troop is also planning a big celebration for Girl Scout Founder Juliette Gordon Low’s birthday on October 31 and hopes to continue serving the community through service projects.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>“To feel that you were able to help mentor and guide girls in achieving their goals and to see the smiles on their faces when they accomplish them is worth the little bit of time you have to offer during the week or month,” said Stevenson.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Through serving girls and helping them to make a difference in their communities, these volunteers are giving back to the community that has given so much to them.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Girl Scouts is still in need of volunteers to help serve girls in the Golden Triangle area. For more information on ways you can volunteer, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gssjc.org/&quot;>www.gssjc.org&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Girl Scouts of the USA is the world's preeminent organization for girls, with a membership of more than 3.2 million girls and adults. Girl Scouting builds girls of courage, confidence, and character, who make the world a better place. Chartered by GSUSA to provide Girl Scouting locally, Girl Scouts of San Jacinto Council is the second largest Girl Scout council in the country serving more than 63,000 girls and 19,000 adults in 26 southeast Texas counties.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                    textIsRich="true">
                    <image
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-10-07T12:04:35.483-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="mtolbert"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                        fileReference="/content/dam/gssjc/news-images/VolunteerPortArthur_Web.jpg"
                        imageRotate="0"/>
                </text>
            </par>
        </middle>
    </jcr:content>
    <_x0032_014/>
</jcr:root>
