<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.776-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="admin"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.843-04:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="admin"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.778-04:00"
        cq:lastRolledoutBy="admin"
        cq:template="/apps/girlscouts/templates/three-column-page"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship,mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Health History and Insurance "
        jcr:uuid="ae4ad127-65fb-4045-a520-a45d2d550b87"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/three-column-page"
        hideInNav="true">
        <content
            cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.707-04:00"
            cq:lastRolledoutBy="admin"
            jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship]"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <middle
                cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.723-04:00"
                cq:lastRolledoutBy="admin"
                jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship]"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                <par
                    cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.731-04:00"
                    cq:lastRolledoutBy="admin"
                    jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship]"
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="foundation/components/parsys">
                    <title
                        cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.761-04:00"
                        cq:lastRolledoutBy="admin"
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-07-07T17:25:53.675-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="kstavisky"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.760-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="kstavisky"
                        jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship]"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/title"
                        title="Health Histories"
                        type="h4"/>
                    <text
                        cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.767-04:00"
                        cq:lastRolledoutBy="admin"
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-07-07T17:26:04.827-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="kstavisky"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.766-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="kstavisky"
                        jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship]"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;p>It is important for you to be aware of any medications, allergies, and health histories a girl may have.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xa;&lt;li>Medication, including over-the-counter products, must never be dispensed without prior written permission from a girl’s custodial parent or guardian. (Your council can provide this form.) Some girls may need to carry and administer their own medications, such as bronchial inhalers, an EpiPen, or diabetes medication.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Common food allergies include dairy products, eggs, soy, wheat, peanuts, tree nuts, and seafood. This means that, before serving any food (such as peanut butter and jelly sandwiches, cookies, or chips), &lt;b>ask&lt;/b> whether anyone is allergic to peanuts, dairy products, or wheat! Even Girl Scout Daisies and Brownies should be aware of their allergies, but double-checking with their parents/guardians is always a good idea.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                    <title_0
                        cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.770-04:00"
                        cq:lastRolledoutBy="admin"
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-07-07T17:26:59.391-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="kstavisky"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.769-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="kstavisky"
                        jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship]"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/title"
                        title="Insurance"
                        type="h4"/>
                    <text_0
                        cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.775-04:00"
                        cq:lastRolledoutBy="admin"
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-07-07T17:27:12.942-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="kstavisky"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.774-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="kstavisky"
                        jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship]"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;p>Every registered Girl Scout and registered adult member in the Girl Scout movement is automatically covered under the basic plan upon registration. The entire premium cost for this protection is borne by Girl Scouts of the USA. The basic plan is effective during the regular fiscal year (October to the following October). Up to 14 months of insurance coverage is provided for new members who register in the month of August. This insurance provides up to a specified maximum for medical expenses incurred as a result of an accident while a member is participating in an approved, supervised Girl Scout activity, after the individual’s primary insurance pays out. This is one reason that all adults and girls should be registered members. Non-registered parents, tagalongs (brothers, sisters, friends), and other persons are not covered by basic coverage.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>This insurance coverage is &lt;b>not&lt;/b> intended to diminish the need for, or replace family health insurance. When $130 in benefits has been paid for covered accident, medical, or dental expense, any subsequent benefits will be payable only for expenses incurred that aren’t compensable under another insurance policy. If there is no family insurance or healthcare program, a specified maximum of medical benefits is available.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>An optional plan of activity insurance is available for Girl Scouts taking extended trips and for non-members who participate in Girl Scout activities. These plans are secondary insurance that a council may offer to cover participants taking part in any council-approved, supervised Girl Scout activity. Optional insurance coverage is available for any Girl Scout activity that involves non-Girl Scouts or lasts longer than three days and two nights. Contact your council to find out how to apply. Your council may make this mandatory, in some cases, particularly for overseas travel.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </par>
            </middle>
        </content>
        <image
            cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.778-04:00"
            cq:lastRolledoutBy="admin"
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-09-25T11:00:26.776-04:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="mgarg"
            jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship]"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            imageRotate="0"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
