<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2015-04-10T13:55:30.275-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="drodgers"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2015-04-10T13:55:35.080-04:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="drodgers"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:scaffolding="/etc/scaffolding/gateway/event"
        cq:tags="[gateway:program-level/ags,gateway:categories/stem,gateway:program-level/cadettes,gateway:program-level/ambassadors,gateway:program-level/senior]"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="She's a Park Explorer (CSA)"
        jcr:uuid="07cfa876-4428-4696-9a62-d6682b858b00"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/event-page">
        <data
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            address="12087 Sw Us Highway 27, Fort White, FL 32038"
            details="&lt;p>At Ichetucknee Springs State Park, many springs combine together to make one gigantic spring run, the Ichetucknee River!&amp;nbsp; This river is one of the most pristine in Florida.&amp;nbsp; Not only is it great fun to canoe, snorkel, and tube, but the Ichetucknee River is also home to an amazing variety of plants and animals.&amp;nbsp; Park rangers work hard to keep the river clean and protected.&amp;nbsp; To make sure it stays healthy, they use many tools to determine its condition, such as monitoring chemicals in the water, measuring its flow, and keeping watch on its wildlife.&amp;nbsp; Learn about these techniques through hands-on activities that will include a demonstration of how the aquifer works, fun games, water-sampling, and protecting aquatic animals.&amp;nbsp;This event costs $7 per person. Limited to 20 people per session.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
            end="{Date}2015-04-25T15:00:00.000-04:00"
            locationLabel="Ichetucknee Springs State Park"
            register="http://girlscouts-gateway.doubleknot.com/event/shes-a-park-explorer-csa-04-25-15-ichetucknee-springs-state-park/1683355"
            srchdisp="At Ichetucknee Springs State Park, many springs combine together to make one gigantic spring run, the Ichetucknee River!  This river is one of the most pristine in Florida.  Not only is it great fun to canoe, snorkel, and tube, but the Ichetucknee River is also home to an amazing variety of plants and animals.  Park rangers work hard to keep the river clean and protected.  To make sure it stays healthy, they use many tools to determine its condition, such as monitoring chemicals in the water, measuring its flow, and keeping watch on its wildlife.  Learn about these techniques through hands-on activities that will include a demonstration of how the aquifer works, fun games, water-sampling, and protecting aquatic animals. This event costs $7 per person."
            start="{Date}2015-04-25T13:00:00.008-04:00">
            <image
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-04-10T13:55:30.271-04:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="drodgers"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                imageRotate="0"/>
        </data>
    </jcr:content>
    <_x0032_015/>
</jcr:root>
