<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2016-01-06T11:21:21.524-05:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
        cq:scaffolding="/etc/scaffolding/gateway/event"
        cq:tags="[gateway:categories/girl-events]"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="She's a Park Explorer at Ichetucknee Springs State Park- DBJ"
        jcr:uuid="635f39be-1bcc-40bb-a986-7c39980fc1cb"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/event-page">
        <data
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            address="12087 SW U.S. Highway 27, Fort White, FL 32038"
            color="#EC008C"
            details="&lt;p>She’s a Park Explorer at Ichetucknee Springs State Park- DBJ&lt;br>&#xa;Grades: K, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Springs and their runs are described as one of the most productive freshwater systems on planet Earth.&amp;nbsp; At Ichetucknee Springs State Park, many springs combine together to make one gigantic spring run, the Ichetucknee River!&amp;nbsp; This river is one of the most pristine in Florida.&amp;nbsp; Not only is it great fun to canoe, snorkel, and tube, but the Ichetucknee River is also home to an amazing variety of plants and animals.&amp;nbsp; Park rangers work hard to keep the river clean and protected.&amp;nbsp; To make sure it stays healthy, they use many tools to determine its condition, such as monitoring chemicals in the water, measuring its flow, and keeping watch on its wildlife.&amp;nbsp; We are going to be learning about some of these techniques, and hands-on activities will include a demonstration of how the aquifer works, fun games, water-sampling, and protecting aquatic animals. Fun patch provided. Park entrance fee included.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;*This event is for 2016 registered Girl Scouts, and registered &amp;amp; approved adult volunteers.&lt;br>&#xa;* For safety and supervision reasons, troops and individuals are not permitted to bring non-Girl Scouts or siblings.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;*Girl/adult ratios must be followed and adults are expected to stay on the premises during the event.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;$8/girl, $8/adult&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;Contact: Brittany McCallister 904.389.3071&lt;/p>&#xa;"
            end="{Date}2016-04-02T12:00:00.000-04:00"
            locationLabel="Ichetucknee Springs State Park"
            register="http://girlscouts-gateway.doubleknot.com/event/shes-a-park-explorer-at-ichetucknee-springs-state-park-dbj/1826253"
            start="{Date}2016-04-02T10:00:00.008-04:00">
            <image
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2016-01-06T11:21:21.517-05:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                fileReference="/content/dam/gateway/pageImgs/Council Program Event.png"
                imageRotate="0"/>
        </data>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
