<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2014-08-27T17:06:57.155-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="spollack"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2014-08-27T17:06:59.011-04:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="spollack"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:scaffolding="/etc/scaffolding/gssjc/news"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Humble Girl Scouts Promote Innovation, Host Intellectual Property Workshop"
        jcr:uuid="50c36e64-66ae-4d94-8b6a-059ebce3399e"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/news-page"
        date="{Date}2014-08-07T17:05:13.000-04:00">
        <middle jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <par jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                <text
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="foundation/components/textimage"
                    text="&lt;p>Humble-area Girl Scouts from San Jacinto Council (GSSJC), one of the largest Girl Scout councils in the U.S., will host an Intellectual Property (IP) patch workshop Saturday, Sept. 27 from 10 a.m. to 3:30 p.m. at the First United Methodist Church (FUMC) of Humble as part of the &lt;i>It’s Your Story-Tell It&lt;/i> Leadership Journey series.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>“Two of the attorneys I work with approached me with the desire to teach girls about intellectual property, so our troops at First United Methodist Church of Humble will host this unique opportunity,” said GSSJC Volunteer Sharon Taylor. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The &lt;i>It's Your Story –&lt;/i>&lt;b> &lt;/b>&lt;i>Tell It!&lt;/i> Leadership Journey series, made possible by a grant from the Dove Self-Esteem Fund, gives girls the opportunity to tell their stories through a range of creative approaches. The Intellectual Property patch curriculum was developed by Girl Scouts District of Colombia with support from the Intellectual Property Education Foundation and the United States Patent and Trademark Office to create a fun, accessible and interesting way to teach girls the importance of innovation and intellectual property to their lives and the national economy. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The IP patch teaches girls the difference between trademarks, copyrights and patents, teaches girls about entrepreneurship and gives girls the opportunity to repurpose an invention created by Girl Scout Founder Juliette Gordon Low.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The workshop is $15 and open to registered Girl Scouts in grades 2-10 (Girl Scout Brownies through Seniors). Girl Scouts who attend the workshop and complete the respective activities for their Girl Scout level will earn the IP patch. To register for the event, contact Sharon Taylor at staylor8682@gmail.com or 713-876-7551. The registration deadline for this workshop is September 13.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                    textIsRich="true">
                    <image
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-08-27T17:05:47.582-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="spollack"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                        fileReference="/content/dam/gssjc/camp-images/Humble.jpg"
                        imageRotate="0"/>
                </text>
            </par>
        </middle>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
