<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2014-10-06T11:28:29.966-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="admin"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2014-10-06T11:28:33.418-04:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="menzor"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:template="/apps/girlscouts/templates/three-column-page"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Camp Registration"
        jcr:uuid="1538be1e-1eb4-43f5-91ab-84c33319bb05"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/three-column-page"
        seoTitle="Camp Registration | Girl Scouts of San Jacinto">
        <content jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <middle jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                <par
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="foundation/components/parsys">
                    <text_0
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-08-21T14:59:11.086-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="spollack"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-08-21T14:59:21.785-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="spollack"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;img src=&quot;/content/dam/gssjc/camp-images/Registration.png&quot;>&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                    <title
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-08-21T12:42:43.531-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="kcharles"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-08-21T12:42:43.531-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="kcharles"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/title"/>
                    <text
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-08-21T12:42:47.058-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="kcharles"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-08-25T10:51:23.594-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="spollack"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Registering for Resident Camp&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/b>Registration for sessions can be done online or by mail or fax. Online registration is recommended because placement is immediate with online registration. You will know instantly if your camper has made it into the session or if she will be placed on the waitlist.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>To register via mail or fax, use the registration form. Please note that faxed or mailed registration forms can take up to five business days to process.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Your registration includes the camp session activities, a camp T-shirt and patch (both given at camp on the last day). You may also choose to pre-pay your Trading Post or Ship’s Store allowance upon registration.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Confirmations&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/b>Those registering online will receive immediate confirmation to the email address on file with the camper’s membership profile. Those registering via mail or fax will receive an email confirmation once their registration has been processed. This could take up to five business days after it is received at the main GSSJC office.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>**Please note that all registration confirmations and camp communications are sent via email.&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp;We use the email address that is noted on your camper’s membership profile. Please make sure you are using a valid and current email address to avoid missing any important information and reminders that may be sent out before camp. Any changes to your current email address on file can be made online via the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://gssjc.ebiz.uapps.net/VP/default.aspx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; adhocenable=&quot;false&quot;>activities registration site&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Waitlist Registration&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/b>When a camp session is full, there is an option to register for the session on a waitlist. When registering for a waitlist spot, you must pay either the deposit or the entire camp fee to hold that spot on the waitlist. If a girl is not placed in the camp session from the waitlist, a full refund will be processed. New sessions may be created based on waiting list.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                    <text_2
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-08-25T10:49:06.392-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="spollack"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-08-25T10:50:41.416-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="spollack"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>&lt;img src=&quot;/content/dam/all_icons/icons_64/money1_64.png&quot;>&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                    <text_1
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-08-25T10:48:27.709-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="spollack"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-09-10T09:34:27.063-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="spollack"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Payments&lt;br>&#xa; &lt;/b>A $50 deposit per session is required for all registrations, with the exception of those requesting a full campership. You are free to make payments at any time on your camp balance. Payment in full is due no later than April 30, 2014.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>After the due date, we will send an invoice to each registrant’s address on file noting any remaining balance. Some of our sessions are quite popular and do draw large waiting lists. After April 30, we reserve the right to place someone on the waiting list in your space if you have not paid your balance.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Failure to pay the balance in full prior to the due date could result in loss of placement.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Payment Installments&lt;br>&#xa; &lt;/b>Once you register, you are free to make layaway payments to your camp balance as often as you’d like. Payments can be sent to: GSSJC Resident Camp Registrars, 3110 Southwest Fwy., Houston, Texas 77098. &lt;b>Incremental payments cannot be made online.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Make sure to note the camper's name, week and session on the check or money order so payments are properly credited. There is no limit on the number of payments you make to your camp balance. However, GSSJC asks that each payment be a minimum of $10. The April 30 payment due date still applies to those taking advantage of our payment installments option.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>***All registrations made after April 30, 2014 must be paid in full.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>** A $50 session change fee applies to all session changes requested after registering.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Online Balance Pay&lt;br>&#xa; &lt;/b>&lt;a href=&quot;https://gssjc.ebiz.uapps.net/VP/default.aspx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; adhocenable=&quot;false&quot;>Pay your resident camp balance online now&lt;/a>&lt;b>.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>Log in to your online account. Go to your “My Family” screen, and choose “Family Order History”. Choose your order from the list and proceed to process payment on the order. If you need assistance with paying your daughter’s fees online, email the GSSJC Customer Service Department at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:customerservice@sjgs.org&quot;>customerservice@sjgs.org&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;or call 713-292-0310 for assistance. Customer Service hours are 8 a.m. – 5 p.m., Monday through Friday.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Refunds&lt;br>&#xa; &lt;/b>The $50 deposit is nonrefundable and nontransferable.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>If you cancel in writing by April 30, 2014, a full refund of all camp fees paid, minus the $50 nonrefundable and nontransferable deposit, will be made.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Cancellations after April 30, 2014 will only result in a refund (minus the deposit), if a camper from the waitlist can take your camper’s spot. (Please note that this is not a guarantee.)&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Should a medical issue arise prior to camp check in your camper can be rescheduled into a later session, if available, at no charge. If that option is not possible, a refund of the remaining balance will be made, minus the deposit.&amp;nbsp;&lt;b>Rescheduling or a refund due to a medical reason can only be made with a note from a doctor.&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp;&lt;b>You must notify the resident camp registrars of an illness in order to reschedule or receive a refund by calling 713-292-0370 no later than the first day of your camper’s session.&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp;All documentation must be received by August 15, 2014 in order to process any refunds. Refunds will not be processed until all documentation is received.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Should your camper need to change to another session or week due to non-medical reasons, requests will be accommodated based on availability. A session change fee of $50 per change will be added to your account.&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                    <text_4
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-08-25T10:52:44.431-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="spollack"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-08-25T10:53:34.128-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="spollack"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>&lt;img src=&quot;/content/dam/all_icons/brainy_icons_64/flower_64.png&quot;>&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                    <text_3
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-08-25T10:51:45.228-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="spollack"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-09-09T15:42:13.186-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="lballanco"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Cookie Dough&lt;br>&#xa; &lt;/b>Girls who earn Cookie Dough by participating in the Girl Scout Cookie Program can apply a portion or all Cookie Dough toward the balance of the camp fee by sending the original Cookie Dough with the payment form. Cookie Dough may not be used toward the down payment.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Camperships&lt;br>&#xa; &lt;/b>Financial assistance for resident camp, called a Campership, is partially underwritten by GSSJC. The remainder of the money comes from donations. To apply for a Campership, fill out the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;/content/dam/gssjc/documents/summer-camp/CampershipApplication2014.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; adhocenable=&quot;false&quot;>campership application form&lt;/a>. You are required to pay the $50 deposit unless you are applying for a full campership.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;br>&#xa;If applying for a full campership or if registering via fax or mail, please return the Campership Application and the registration form in the same envelope with any payments you will be making. Camperships cover the cost of the camp session only and do not include Trading Post/Ship’s Store allowances or camp packs.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Camperships are awarded on a first-come, first-served basis and requests for camperships are due no later than April 15, 2014. Requests received after that date will be made only if funds are available. A committee of volunteers will review your completed application, and you will receive notification if you are awarded a campership. Camperships are awarded based on individual family’s needs. The information collected from your confidential application is not used for any other purpose.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Want to help send a girl to camp?&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp;Anyone wishing to make a contribution to the Campership Fund may send a check to:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>GSSJC Campership Fund&lt;br>&#xa;3110 Southwest Fwy.&lt;br>&#xa;Houston, TX 77098&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Indicate this is the fund to which you wish to contribute by writing “campership donation” on the memo line. Your contribution is tax deductible.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Membership&lt;br>&#xa; &lt;/b>Each camper is encouraged, but not required, to register as a member of Girl Scouts of San Jacinto Council before they come to camp. Girls who are not registered members of GSSJC for the 2014-2015 membership year may register or renew their membership online and pay the $15 registration fee.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>If you are unsure what level your girl is in, see the chart below. All grades are as of fall 2015:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Girl Scout Daisies&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp;- Kindergarten and 1st grade&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Girl Scout Brownies&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp;- 2nd and 3rd grade&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Girl Scout Juniors&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp;- 4th and 5th grade&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Girl Scout Cadettes&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp;- 6th, 7th and 8th grade&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Girl Scout Seniors&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp;- 9th and 10th grade&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Girl Scout Ambassadors&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp;- 11th and 12th grade&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Girl Scouting is open to all girls in grades kindergarten through 12th grade and to adults, both women and men, who subscribe to the Girl Scout Promise and Law.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </par>
            </middle>
        </content>
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2014-08-25T11:59:11.945-04:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="lballanco"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            imageRotate="0"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
