<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-24T09:19:41.976-05:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
        cq:template="/apps/girlscouts/templates/three-column-page"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:lockable,mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Women of Distinction"
        jcr:uuid="03ab4426-5666-4fe3-a16a-978302aa4124"
        sling:redirect="true"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/three-column-page"
        sling:vanityPath="http://www.girlscouts-gateway.org:80/content/gateway/wod"
        seoTitle="Women of Distinction | Girl Scouts of Gateway Council">
        <content jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <middle jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                <par
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="foundation/components/parsys">
                    <text_1
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-11-21T08:38:14.292-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="bmoore"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-08-19T13:17:33.158-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;h3 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>&lt;b>2016 Women of Distinction&lt;/b>&lt;/h3>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                    <text
                        jcr:created="{Date}2014-11-14T12:59:42.347-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="bmoore"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-23T13:41:25.227-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;p>The Women of Distinction is a signature fundraising event to honor outstanding Northeast Florida Women for their professional accomplishments, service to others and community impact. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>&lt;img src=&quot;/content/dam/all_icons/event_icons/event_awards.png&quot;>&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                    <image
                        jcr:created="{Date}2015-11-13T16:48:35.681-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="dpage"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-13T16:49:16.354-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/image"
                        fileReference="/content/dam/gateway/pageImgs/12227700_10150675543554977_5336646974633318544_n.jpg"
                        imageRotate="0"/>
                    <text_2
                        jcr:created="{Date}2015-11-13T16:49:49.900-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="dpage"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-16T14:27:33.484-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>2016 Honorees: Vickie Cavey, Stephanie Cost, Cheryl Bryan, Heather Duncan, Debbie Buckland. &lt;/b>&lt;i>Not pictured: Velma Monteiro-Tribble&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                    <text_0
                        jcr:created="{Date}2015-08-19T13:17:17.296-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="dpage"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-23T13:42:09.676-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Event Details&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Date: April 7, 2016&lt;br>&#xa;Time: 6-7:15 pm Social hour &amp;amp; Silent Auction&lt;br>&#xa;7:15-8:30 pm Dinner and Program&lt;br>&#xa;Place: Jacksonville Marriott&lt;br>&#xa;4670 Salisbury Rd.&lt;br>&#xa;Jacksonville, FL&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Tickets are $100/per person and sponsorship opportunities are currently available.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>For tickets, sponsorship opportunities, and other inquiries, please contact:&lt;br>&#xa;Robert Watts&lt;br>&#xa;Senior Director of Development&lt;br>&#xa;(904) 421-3485&lt;br>&#xa;rwatts@girlscouts-gateway.org&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                    <textimage
                        jcr:created="{Date}2015-11-13T16:54:07.086-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="dpage"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-23T14:49:44.371-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/textimage"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Debbie Buckland&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Debbie is Market President for Branch Banking &amp;amp; Trust Company (BB&amp;amp;T) in Jacksonville, FL.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Debbie currently serves as Chair of Downtown Vision, Inc. and on the boards of JAX Chamber, River Garden Foundation and First Coast YMCA. Debbie is also a past chair of Jacksonville Women’s Business Center and American Cancer Society. She is a member of Wolfson Children’s Hospital Women’s Board, Jacksonville Women’s Network, Women’s Giving Alliance and is currently serving on the Campaign Cabinet for United Way of Northeast Florida.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Debbie was named a 2006 Woman of Influence by the Jacksonville Business Journal, is a 2009 Graduate of Leadership Jacksonville and in 2011 was named by the Mayor’s Commission on the Status of Women as one of Jacksonville’s &lt;i>Women Making a Difference.&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Debbie is a graduate of Emory &amp;amp; Henry College in Emory, Virginia with a Bachelor of Arts in Business &amp;amp; Economics and Philosophy.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true">
                        <image
                            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-23T14:49:44.371-05:00"
                            jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                            fileReference="/content/dam/gateway/pageImgs/Buckland, Debbie.jpg"
                            height="200"
                            imageRotate="0"
                            width="175"/>
                    </textimage>
                    <textimage_5
                        jcr:created="{Date}2015-11-16T10:14:49.402-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="dpage"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-23T14:48:23.323-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/textimage"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Cheryl Bryan&lt;br>&#xa; &lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Cheryl is a retired educator who focused on biology and science at Episcopal School in Jacksonville, Florida. In addition, Cheryl is an active volunteer in the Jacksonville community.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Cheryl was a Girl Scout locally in Jacksonville, Florida and recalls her experience at camp as a highlight of her scouting time. Cheryl says scouting gave her a sense of commitment and achievement and she always loved earning badges.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Cheryl is a sustainer of the Junior League of Jacksonville, where she has served terms as Community Vice-President, Vice Chair of the tennis tournament at Amelia Island, as well as serving as a board member for several years.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Cheryl has also served in an educational capacity for the following organizations: Riverside Presbyterian Day School, The Bartram School, The Bolles School, Children's Home Society, Girl Scouts of Gateway Council, St. Vincent's Foundation, the American Cancer Society, and the DePaul Society.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Cheryl has been honored as a Life Member of the American Cancer Society and received the Eve Lifetime Achievement Award in 2012.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Cheryl is a magna cum laude graduate of Wheaton College in Norton, Massachusetts.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true">
                        <image
                            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-23T14:48:23.323-05:00"
                            jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                            fileReference="/content/dam/gateway/pageImgs/Cheryl Bryan.jpg"
                            height="200"
                            imageRotate="0"
                            width="175"/>
                    </textimage_5>
                    <textimage_0
                        jcr:created="{Date}2015-11-13T16:56:46.995-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="dpage"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-23T14:49:13.125-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/textimage"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Stephanie Cost&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Stephanie is currently the First Lady of Jacksonville University. Her role entails being a strategic planner, fundraiser, advisor and ambassador to the university at large.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Stephanie was a Girl Scout in Syracuse, New York in the 1960s. In 6th grade, Stephanie was the troop's biggest cookie seller. She remained in scouting through Cadettes. Later, her daughter, Melanie, became a Brownie and rose through the scouting ranks. Stephanie became co-leader for Melanie's Junior troop. Stephanie says scouting gave her a circle beyond her family that shared her same beliefs and she wanted to share these positive experiences with her daughter.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Stephanie has experience serving as an&amp;nbsp;Advisory Board member for the Jacksonville University Career Development Center, Program Coordinator for the Delores Barr Weaver Fellows Program, Steering Committee Member for the Women’s Giving Alliance,&amp;nbsp;Board member and Strategic Planning Committee member for the Ronald McDonald House Jacksonville, and Board member for the Cathedral Arts Program.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Stephanie is a graduate of Immaculata University in Frazer, Pennsylvania with a Bachelor of Arts in Economics where she graduated summa cum laude in her class.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true">
                        <image
                            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-23T14:49:13.125-05:00"
                            jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                            fileReference="/content/dam/gateway/pageImgs/ju_stephaniecost_Editorial_JU_web.jpg"
                            height="200"
                            imageRotate="0"
                            width="175"/>
                    </textimage_0>
                    <textimage_3
                        jcr:created="{Date}2015-11-16T10:07:18.665-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="dpage"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-24T09:19:41.968-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/textimage"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Vickie Cavey&lt;br>&#xa; &lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Vickie is the Director of Strategy Development and Execution at JEA. She is responsible for leading the creation and implementation of JEA's Strategic Plan for the CEO and Executive Team. Vickie has been with the company since 1984 and has held a variety of roles that have been stepping stones to where she is today.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Vickie has served on several committees and boards within the community including: United Way of Northeast Florida, Jacksonville Women's Network, Pine Castle, Big Brothers/Big Sisters of Northeast Florida, Mayor's Commission on the Status of Women, JCCI, WJCT, MaliVai Washington Youth Foundation, Haven Hospice, and St. Vincent's Foundation. Vickie is a 2007 Leadership Jacksonville graduate.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Vickie has received several awards for her community service including: Woman of Influence Award (2007), President's Volunteer Service Award (2007), and Volunteer Jacksonville Service Award (2008).&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Vickie is a graduate of the University of Florida where she received her Bachelor of Science in Mechanical Engineering.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true">
                        <image
                            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-24T09:19:41.968-05:00"
                            jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                            fileReference="/content/dam/gateway/pageImgs/Vickie Cavey Head Shot.jpg"
                            height="200"
                            imageRotate="0"
                            width="175"/>
                    </textimage_3>
                    <textimage_1
                        jcr:created="{Date}2015-11-16T10:04:42.306-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="dpage"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-23T14:47:17.639-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/textimage"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Heather Duncan&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Heather Duncan currently serves as Regional Director of External Affairs for AT&amp;amp;T Florida. She has worked in the telecommunications industry for over twenty-five years and with AT&amp;amp;T since 1994, with a primary focus in advertising, marketing, public relations, community and governmental affairs.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>She is a member of Leadership Jacksonville and Leadership Florida. The Jacksonville Business Journal named her one of the top five executives of large companies in 2007 and one of their “2008 Women of Influence.”&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>This year, Heather is serving as Chairman of Gator Bowl Sports, which includes the Taxslayer Bowl, the Jacksonville Sports Council and JAXSPORTS Charities. She also serves on the boards of the Jacksonville Regional Chamber of Commerce, the Mayor’s Advisory Commission on Television, Motion Picture and Commercial Production, Dreams Come True of Jacksonville as a past president, JAXBIZ and the JAXUSA Partnership Policy Council.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>She has previously served on the boards of Cathedral Arts Project, Volunteers in Medicine, the advisory council for UNF’s Coggin College of Business and the Jacksonville Downtown Rotary Club where she received the Paul Harris Award for community service.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Heather is a graduate of the University of Southern Mississippi.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true">
                        <image
                            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-23T14:47:17.639-05:00"
                            jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                            fileReference="/content/dam/gateway/pageImgs/Heather Duncan photo.jpg"
                            height="200"
                            imageRotate="0"
                            width="175"/>
                    </textimage_1>
                    <textimage_4
                        jcr:created="{Date}2015-11-16T10:09:28.218-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="dpage"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-23T14:49:29.655-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/textimage"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Velma Monteiro-Tribble&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Velma Monteiro-Tribble is currently the Director of Grants and Programs at the Florida Blue Foundation. Prior to this position, she was Chief Operating Officer and Assistant Treasurer at Alcoa Foundation, Pittsburgh, PA, and New York, NY. Velma also served as an executive with the W.K. Kellogg Foundation (WKKF). She has more than 30 years of work experience and expertise in philanthropic giving worldwide, grantmaking, leadership development and training, community development, community enterprise, evaluation, and tests and measurements, with such organizations as the National Association for Community Leadership, the U.S. Department of Education, American College Testing, Rhode Island College and Brown University. She also served as an administrator in the U.S. Peace Corps in Asia.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>She has received numerous awards for her work, including the Urban Bankers Leadership Award and the National Woman of Achievement Award from the National Business and Professional Women Association, higher education awards, Outstanding Woman in the Material World Award from the Women and Girls Foundation, and One of the 50 Most Influential Women Award from the &lt;i>Pittsburgh Courier&lt;/i>. She is currently under contract to complete her book on women aspiring to take on leadership roles in the Corporate Suites (the C-Suites).&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>She currently serves on the boards of several nonprofits, including Florida State College System Foundation, Jacksonville Urban League, Jacksonville Women’s Giving Alliance, and the Jacksonville Ritz Chamber Players. She is a past chair of the Advisory Board for the Morehouse College International Leadership Center and has served on the boards of Seton Hall University, Highmark Foundation, Tampa Bay Community Foundation, and WQED Public Broadcasting, and other local, national and international boards.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Velma holds a Bachelor of Science degree from Stillman College, and a nonprofit management certificate from Case Western Reserve.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true">
                        <image
                            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-23T14:49:29.655-05:00"
                            jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="foundation/components/image"
                            fileReference="/content/dam/gateway/pageImgs/Velma.M-9156.jpg"
                            height="200"
                            imageRotate="0"
                            width="175"/>
                    </textimage_4>
                </par>
            </middle>
        </content>
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-11-13T16:52:36.815-05:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            imageRotate="0"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
