<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2016-01-19T14:22:35.273-05:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
        cq:tags="[gateway:categories/cookies]"
        cq:template="/apps/girlscouts/templates/three-column-page"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Cookie FAQ's"
        jcr:uuid="a17dfd80-bb5f-41ab-9acc-c744bf0e10d6"
        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/three-column-page"
        seoTitle="Cookie FAQ's | Girl Scouts of Gateway Council">
        <content jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <middle jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                <par
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="foundation/components/parsys">
                    <title
                        jcr:created="{Date}2015-01-12T10:45:35.512-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="bmoore"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-01-12T10:45:35.512-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="bmoore"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/title"/>
                    <text_0
                        jcr:created="{Date}2015-11-17T09:11:38.830-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="dpage"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2016-01-19T14:21:55.042-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>What are the Cookie Program Dates?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Dec. 28: &amp;nbsp;Cookie Sale Begins&amp;nbsp; Order may be taken&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Girls continue taking orders even after they turn in their initial order to the troop&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Dec 28: Digital Cookie Orders can now be taken&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Jan. 17: Pre-orders must be submitted to Troop Product Sales Managers to submit orders in eBudde&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>o&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Girls continue taking orders after they turn in their initial order to the troop&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Feb. 5- Feb. 6: Cookie distribution to troops&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Feb. 12-Mar. 13: Cookie Booth participation begins&lt;b>&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Who is eligible to sell cookies?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Any actively registered Girl Scout (all age levels from Daisy to Ambassador) is eligible to sell cookies.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;b>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>What skills do girls learn through the Girl Scout Cookie Program?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Goal setting, decision making, money management, people skills, and business ethics are five of the amazing skills your girls will achieve through this exciting program.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Who receives the proceeds for the Cookie Sale?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Troops earn cookie proceeds on each box sold.&amp;nbsp; All other proceeds stay within the 16 counties of our Council boundaries and are invested into our Girl Programs.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>What methods may my troop use to sell cookies?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Troops can use traditional methods of order taking using the cookie order form.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Girls may take orders at workplaces of caregivers, relatives, and friends.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Another great method is to go door-to-door (must have proper adult supervision) and Troop cookie booths.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Girls and their parents may also participate in online cookie sales through the Digital Cookie Program.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Can you sell cookies on Facebook or other online sites?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Cookies may only be sold online through participation in the GSUSA approved Digital Cookie Program.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, and email blasts are acceptable ways to promote cookies.&amp;nbsp; Please adhere to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.girlscouts.org/help/internet_safety_pledge.asp&quot;>Internet Safety Pledge&lt;/a> when using the electronic forum for sales.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Where can I find tips on selling cookies?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Tips can be found on the &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.littlebrowniebakers.com/&quot;>Little Brownie Bakers&lt;/a> website.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Little Brownie Bakers Blog, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pinterest.com/&quot;>Pinterest&lt;/a>, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/&quot;>Facebook&lt;/a>, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.girlscouts-gateway.org/&quot;>Gateway Council&lt;/a>, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tumblr.com/&quot;>Tumblr&lt;/a>, &lt;a href=&quot;http://instagram.com/&quot;>Instagram&lt;/a>, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/&quot;>You Tube&lt;/a>,&amp;nbsp; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/&quot;>Twitter&lt;/a> are wonderful avenues to review for selling tips and ideas.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Which cookie cost $5.00? &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The Toffee-tastic cookies are priced slightly higher at $5.00 a box.&amp;nbsp; Gluten free products in general cost more to produce and are priced higher than products that contain gluten.&amp;nbsp; This is also a limited production product which increases the cost slightly.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Where can the girls get cookie training?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Little Brownie Bakers has designed a training program specifically for our girls named “&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.littlebrowniebakers.com/volunteers/cookie-rookie/&quot;>Cookie Rookie&lt;/a>.”&amp;nbsp; This fun and exciting training is geared towards our first time cookie sellers and is also helpful as a refresher course to any girl who desires it.&amp;nbsp; The entire program only lasts 10-minutes and they have included a discussion guide and meeting activity ideas for our volunteers to download from their website.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Where can I get cookie training?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://vipetraining.littlebrownie.com/Login.aspx&quot;>Cookie VIP eTraining&lt;/a> on the Little Brownie Bakers website and become familiar with all areas of the Little Brownie Bakers website as it includes an amazing array of useful information regarding all things cookies.&amp;nbsp; Little Brownie Bakers also provides a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.littlebrowniebakers.com/volunteers/cookie-rookie/&quot;>Cookie Rookie&lt;/a> training component for girls that include valuable resources for volunteers working with the girls.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Are there shipping costs associated with Digital Cookies?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Yes.&amp;nbsp; When an individual orders cookies via the Digital Cookie 2.0 program they will incur standard shipping fees which are established directly by the vendor who processes and ships the orders for Girl Scouts. &amp;nbsp;Please advise everyone to carefully review the shipping charges prior to finalizing their online cookie purchases.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Who determines the shipping fees?&amp;nbsp; How is the pricing structure determined?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The vendor who processes and ships the online order sets the fees and local councils do not have control over these costs.&amp;nbsp; Girl Scouts of Gateway Council does not set the fee schedule, nor does the vendor compensate the council for fees incurred by the consumer. &amp;nbsp;The pricing structure is based largely on the actual cost of ensuring that the cookies are delivered in a timely manner and incur no damage during the shipping process.&amp;nbsp; Shipping costs are structured around expedited delivery services.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Can you still sell door to door?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Of course you may sell door to door.&amp;nbsp; Girls ages 5-12 must have an adult present with them when selling.&amp;nbsp; Remember that safety is our number one priority and no girl should ever sell alone.&amp;nbsp; You should only sell in neighborhoods that you are familiar with and remember to never give out your home address, last name or enter a home of someone that you do not know.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Can you sell at a flea market or other paid venue?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Yes, please keep in mind that troops are responsible for any fees associated with booth rental.&amp;nbsp; We are unable to reimburse troops who choose this option to sell cookies.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Can our troop take credit card payments for cookie sales?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>You may choose to use this payment method.&amp;nbsp; The troop will be responsible for entering into the merchant agreement and will be responsible for any fees associated with the merchant service.&amp;nbsp; Troops may not raise the price of the box of cookies to “offset” any fees.&amp;nbsp; We are unable to reimburse troops for any fees incurred.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>What is an initial order?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The initial order is the first order submitted in eBudde.&amp;nbsp; The initial order period ends when the Troop Product Sales Manager submits their first order in eBudde.&amp;nbsp; The deadline for the initial order is January 17.&amp;nbsp; If a troop submits the initial order in eBudde prior to that date, then the initial order period is over for that troop.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Do we need to collect money when people pre-order cookies?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>No, only collect money from a purchaser at the time you deliver the product to them.&amp;nbsp; If you do not have the product when you take an order, do not collect money.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Can my girl continue to take cookie orders after the initial order has been submitted?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Absolutely!&amp;nbsp; All girls are encouraged to continue taking orders after the initial order is submitted.&amp;nbsp; The troop will have access to additional cookies from one of several cookie warehouses and cupboards.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Who is able to enter cookie orders into eBudde?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Any registered adult member who has completed the Volunteer Application and background check is eligible to become a Troop Product Sales Manager.&amp;nbsp; They will need to complete the necessary paperwork and training through one of the many Community trainings offered.&amp;nbsp; All trainings are listed on the Council website under “Events.”&amp;nbsp; Once all steps are completed, they will be provided access to eBudde.&amp;nbsp; Please contact your Community Product Sales Manager and they will assist you through this process.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>May I order booth cookies when I submit our troop’s initial order?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Yes, you may order cookies for your booths using the initial order tab.&amp;nbsp; Please be advised that your troop will be responsible for payment of any cookies that your troop takes into possession.&amp;nbsp; We suggest that you only request a small amount for your first weekend of booth sales when you submit your initial order.&amp;nbsp; Additional cookies will be available for pickup beginning February 8 at a Cookie Cupboard.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>How do I obtain a username and password for eBudde?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Users are added to the eBudde system by the Community Product Sales Manager.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Once you have been added to the system, an email message will be sent to notify you.&amp;nbsp; Your username will be your email address and the password will be 1058@RahRah (case sensitive).&amp;nbsp; You will be prompted to change your password when you enter the eBudde system for the first-time.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>If you have not been given a username and password please contact your Community Product Sales Manager or email &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:gscookies@girlscouts-gateway.org&quot;>gscookies@girlscouts-gateway.org&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Can I manually add girls to eBudde?&lt;br>&#xa; &lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;No. To add a girl, the Troop Product Sales Manager is asked to complete the &lt;a href=&quot;/content/gateway/en/about-our-council/forms-documents/request-to-add-girl-to-elude-digital-cookie.html&quot; adhocenable=&quot;false&quot;>eBudde&lt;/a> online request.&amp;nbsp; You will need the girl’s First/Last Name, girl’s GSUSA ID, Troop#, Date of Birth, Grade Level, parent’s First/Last Name, and valid email address.&amp;nbsp; We will promptly add them to the system.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Why aren’t my girls showing up in eBudde?&lt;br>&#xa; &lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;The girl information was imported into eBudde using information from our membership database.&amp;nbsp; The importing process required a valid parent email address and a list of other information in the girl’s record.&amp;nbsp; If any of the required information was missing from the girl’s membership record, the girl’s name could not be added to eBudde during the initial import.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Missing girls are added as the required information is received from the Troop Product Sales Manager.&amp;nbsp; Please ensure that your girl has an active &lt;a href=&quot;https://gsusa.ebiz.uapps.net/vp/default.aspx?pid=6&amp;amp;utm_campaign=gsrecruitmentcampaign_6&amp;amp;utm_medium=hub&amp;amp;utm_source=join&amp;amp;utm_campaign=GSRecruitmentCampaign_6&amp;amp;utm_medium=hub&amp;amp;utm_source=join&quot;>GSUSA membership&lt;/a>.&amp;nbsp; If they are actively registered, then complete the&lt;b> &lt;/b>eBudde online request. You will need the girl’s First/Last Name, girl’s GSUSA ID, Troop#, Date of Birth, Grade Level, parent’s First/Last Name, and valid email address.&amp;nbsp; We will promptly add them to the system.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>I understand that there are nightly uploads into Digital Order Cookie.&amp;nbsp; How long will it take for us to see the changes?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Please give GSUSA a minimum of 48-hours to send you a link for Digital Order Cookie.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Do I need to submit an eBudde/Digital Order Cookie request for any newly registered Girl Scout?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Yes, you will need to request this manually since the girl was not included in the initial upload.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Please submit the request utilizing the eBudde online request tool.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>When will we receive our deposit slips?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>You will receive your deposit slips from your Community Product Sales manager at the time you pick up your initial cookie order.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>How do I order the troop cookies from the Cookie Cupboard?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>After troops have received the initial cookie order, additional cookies will be available at several locations (Cookie Cupboard) throughout our council area.&amp;nbsp; To request additional cookies, Troop Product Sales Managers will place a pending order with one of our Cookie Cupboards prior to the pickup date.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The Troop Product Sales Manager will utilize the eBudde system to place all cookie order requests.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We are going paperless this year at the Hills warehouse locations.&amp;nbsp; Please ensure that all individuals picking up product at these locations has their own eBudde user name and password.&amp;nbsp; Product will not be released to anyone without eBudde access.&amp;nbsp; Please do not share your user name and password with other users.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>How do we choose cookie booths?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The cookie booth locations will be selected through our eBudde system, using the Booth Scheduler.&amp;nbsp; All hot-spot locations for our entire council area will be listed on the Booth Scheduler.&amp;nbsp; Troops may pick from any of the booths listed in the booth scheduler.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Do all parents or chaperones have to complete a background check to work with their daughter at the cookie booth?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Safety is our number one priority!&amp;nbsp; Any individual over the age of 18 must be currently registered with GSUSA (for insurance purposes) and complete a verified background screening prior to working a cookie booth.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Can a Daisy sell at a cookie booth?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Any registered Girl Scout may sell at a Girl Scout cookie booth…this includes all grade levels.&amp;nbsp; Please adhere to proper adult-to-girl ratios which is located in the Volunteer Essentials.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>What is the method you use to determine the amount a troop earns for each package of cookies that is sold?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Troop proceeds are based on the total number of boxes sold by a troop divided by the number of girls participating in the sale.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; This will be the troop’s Per Girl Average (PGA).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Troop Proceeds are based on the PGA.&amp;nbsp; Your PGA will not be impacted by those girls who are listed in eBudde, but do not participate in the sale (as long as no entries have been made under that girl).&amp;nbsp; We have outlined your earnings below:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>1-199 PGA equals 50¢ per box&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>200-299 PGA equals 60¢ per box&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>300-399 PGA equals 70¢ per box&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>400+ PGA equals 85¢ per box&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Who is eligible to Opt Out of receiving cookie rewards?&amp;nbsp; What are the advantages and what patches are the girls eligible to receive?&lt;br>&#xa; &lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/b> The opportunity to Opt Out of receiving Girl Scout Cookie Girl Rewards in exchange for higher proceeds is extended to our Girl Scout Cadette, Senior, and Ambassador Troops.&amp;nbsp; These troops will receive an additional .05 cents per package.&amp;nbsp; This needs to be a unanimous decision among all Girl members of your troop and each Girl in the troop will need to agree and sign the Opt Out Consent Form.&amp;nbsp; Girls in troops that Opt Out will be eligible for these patches (if she meets the individual patch requirements): 2016 Bar, Vitrual Gift of Caring, and/or Cookie Theme.&amp;nbsp; Opt Out forms must be submitted to your Community Product Sales Manager prior to your Troop’s Initial Cookie Order due on January 17, 2016.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>When will our troop receive the proceeds for the cookie sales?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Troop proceeds are based on the sales of each girl participating in the Cookie Program.&amp;nbsp; The total amount of proceeds earned by the girls in the troop is listed on the Troop Sales Report provided in the eBudde system.&amp;nbsp; When depositing payments for the cookies, only the amount due to Girl Scouts of Gateway Council should be deposited into the Product Sales bank account.&amp;nbsp; Each troop will receive a set of bank deposit slips after the initial order is received.&amp;nbsp; Please do not use deposit slips from other troops or over the counter bank deposit slips, this could delay the processing.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>When will girls receive the profit for the online sales?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The online sales are credited to the girls in eBudde immediately following an approved online transaction.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The troop proceeds begin to calculate after the troop’s initial order is submitted and continue to update as additional cookies are allocated the girls.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>How are the Digital Cookie Sales calculated towards each girl’s rewards?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The digital orders are calculated the same way in which we calculate the traditional delivery methods.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Will the Digital Cookie Sales be calculated towards each girl’s initial order rewards?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Yes.&amp;nbsp; Please note:&amp;nbsp; if the Digital Cookie Order is placed before the Troop’s Product Sales Manager submits the initial troop order in eBudde, then it will count towards the girl’s initial rewards.&amp;nbsp; Any digital orders placed after the initial troop order will not count towards the initial rewards&lt;b>&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>What are the requirements to earn the “Virtual Gift of Caring” rewards?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Any girl who sells 15 boxes to a designated Gift of Caring partner “Operation USO” will earn this patch.&amp;nbsp; Any girl who sells 30 or more boxes for Operation USO will also receive the pink camo cinch sack.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Will eBudde automatically calculate each girl’s Digital Cookie Sales on the rewards tab?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Yes, eBudde will consider all digital sales when calculating a girl’s earned rewards.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>When will my girl receive her rewards?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Girl rewards are shipped to the Communities during the week of April 25.&amp;nbsp; The Community Product Sales Manager will notify troops when to pick up their rewards.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>&amp;nbsp;I entered a pending order for cookies, but I did not pick them up at the warehouse.&amp;nbsp; How do I delete this transaction in eBudde?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The pending transaction will be deleted by a staff member after 48-hours of the scheduled pickup date.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>How long does it take for a bank deposit to show up in eBudde?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>We have to manually verify each troop’s bank deposits, so they will not reflect immediately in eBudde.&amp;nbsp; If you make a deposit before 2:00pm Monday-Friday, then it should show up the following business day.&amp;nbsp; Any deposits made after 2:00 pm Monday-Friday or on Saturday will be inputted after two business days.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Are camp credit rewards cumulative?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Yes, the $100 resident camp credit is cumulative up to $200 and may only be used towards full-week resident camp sessions&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Can we use our camp credit rewards for Smile Camp?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>No, camp credits may only be used towards the full-week resident camp at Camp Kateri.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Are camp credit rewards transferable?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>You may transfer your $100 camp credit reward to any actively registered Girl Scout.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;The $425 camp credit reward is not transferable and may only be redeemed by the girl who earned that reward.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;b>Is my purchase of Girl Scout cookies tax-deductible?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;p>&lt;p>&lt;p>&lt;p>&lt;b>No,&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp;if you keep the cookies. If you buy Girl Scout Cookies and take the cookies home (to consume them), you've purchased a product at a fair market value. For this reason, no part of the price of a package of Girl Scout Cookies used in this way is tax-deductible.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Yes,&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp;if you leave the cookies with Girl Scouts as a donation. Many Girl Scouts ask customers to pay for one or more packages of cookies for use in their Take Action/Service projects or &amp;quot;Gift of Caring&amp;quot; programs. Customers not receiving Girl Scout Cookies don't benefit directly from paying for them, so those individuals may treat the purchase price of the donated cookies as a charitable contribution. Additionally, customers may wish to donate cookies they have purchased from a Girl Scout to another organization, which may qualify as a donation to the organization receiving the cookies and may therefore be tax-deductible.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                    <text
                        jcr:created="{Date}2016-01-19T14:22:15.211-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="dpage"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2016-01-19T14:22:35.266-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="dpage"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="girlscouts/components/text"
                        text="&lt;p>For a full list of GSUSA Frequently Asked Questions, click &lt;a adhocenable=&quot;false&quot; href=&quot;http://www.girlscouts.org/en/cookies/all-about-cookies/FAQs.html&quot;>here&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </par>
            </middle>
        </content>
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2015-04-07T09:10:37.143-04:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="drodgers"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            imageRotate="0"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
